Records of the Immigration and Naturalization Service, Series A, Subject Correspondence Files. Part 2, 3, & 4 on Microfilm 6074 mf
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Records of the Immigration and Naturalization Service, Series A, Subject Correspondence Files. Part 2, 3, & 4 on Microfilm
1906-1930
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Immigration and Naturalization Service
6074 mf
6.44 cubic feet
58 microfilm reels
Records, microfilm.
2274856
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, February 23, 2016
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 23, 2016
Biographical / Historical
The United States Immigration and Naturalization Service (INS) was an agency of the U.S. Department of Justice from 19332003. Most of its functions were transferred to three new entities U.S. Citizenship and Immigration Services (USCIS), U.S. Immigration and Customs Enforcement (ICE), and U.S. Customs and Border Protection (CBP) within the newly created Department of Homeland Security, as part of a major government reorganization following the September 11 attacks of 2001.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Asians--United States--History--20th century--Sources.; Mexicans--United States--History--20th century--Sources.; United States--Emigration and immigration--History--Sources.; United States--Emigration and immigration--Government policy--History-- Sources.; Boehm, Randolph.; Kraut, Alan M.; Lester, Robert.; United States. Immigration and Naturalization Service--Archives.; United States. Immigration and Naturalization Service.; University Publications of America (Firm)
2274856
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 1)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 2)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 3)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 4)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 5)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 6)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 7)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 8)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 9)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 10)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 11)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 12)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 13)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 14)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 15)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 16)
- Records of ImmigrationPt.2: Mexican Immigration, 1906-1930 (Reel 17)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 18)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 19)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 20)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 21)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 22)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 23)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 24)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 25)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 26)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 27)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 28)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 29)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 30)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 31)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 32)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 33)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 34)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 3: Ellis Island - 1900-1933 (Reel 35)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 36)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 37)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 38)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 39)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 40)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 41)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 42)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 43)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 44)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 4: European investigations, 1898-1936 (Reel 45)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 5: Prostitution (Reel 46)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 5: Prostitution (Reel 47)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 5: Prostitution (Reel 48)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 5: Prostitution (Reel 49)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 5: Prostitution (Reel 50)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 5: Prostitution (Reel 51)
- Records of the Immigration.Pt. 5: Prostitution (Reel 52)